<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lambda Matters</title>
    <link>https://lambdamatters.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Lambda Matters</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://lambdamatters.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://lambdamatters.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lambdamatters.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>We ♥ Haskell, and Functional Programming.
But how did this come about in the first place ?
Well, we too started out programming in C, C++, &amp;amp; Java with a bit of scripting languages here and there. But our secret passion lay in LISP &amp;amp; its dialects like Scheme, to which we got introduced by the legendary Structure and Interpretation of Computer Programs.
Our own experience with imperative followed by object-oriented programming, and the recent work with huge amounts of JavaScript frameworks got us convinced that Functional Programming was the way to go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Consulting And Services</title>
      <link>https://lambdamatters.github.io/service/consulting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lambdamatters.github.io/service/consulting/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t think they tried to market it to the billionaire, spelunking, base-jumping crowd. i did the same thing to gandhi, he didn&amp;rsquo;t eat for three weeks. i once heard a wise man say there are no perfect men.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rahgu Ugare</title>
      <link>https://lambdamatters.github.io/raghu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lambdamatters.github.io/raghu/</guid>
      <description>Raghu is passionate about getting people to love math, science and programming. He is fond of books, movies, music, fonts, exploring different programming paradigms and languages, and can be frequently found experimenting on numbers, algorithms and patterns using Mathematica. He has experience designing and developing SOA-based platforms for clients in Europe, US &amp;amp; the Middle East.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Training And Workshops</title>
      <link>https://lambdamatters.github.io/service/training/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lambdamatters.github.io/service/training/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t think they tried to market it to the billionaire, spelunking, base-jumping crowd. i did the same thing to gandhi, he didn&amp;rsquo;t eat for three weeks. i once heard a wise man say there are no perfect men.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vijay Anant</title>
      <link>https://lambdamatters.github.io/vijay/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lambdamatters.github.io/vijay/</guid>
      <description>Vijay has a passion for technology and teaching. He has also volunteered to teach during his free time, and has a penchant for history, anime, and poetry. Generally interested in technology as a whole, has occasionally fiddled with many programming languages and tech. His expertise lies in SOA and related integration technologies. Vijay has consulted for many major clients in India and Europe.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>